<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on </title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Tic-tac-toe bot</title>
      <link>/post/tic-tac-toe-bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/tic-tac-toe-bot/</guid>
      <description>Riddles.io is a platform were you can practice your AI skills. You can compete with other groups or persons on different challenges. For all those challenges you have to program an agent or bot that takes actions depending on what your opponents do. One of those challenges is about playing the game of ultimate tic tac toe. This a more complex, and more interesting, version of the classical tic tac toe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voting Recommender</title>
      <link>/post/voting-recommender/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/voting-recommender/</guid>
      <description>In the Netherlands we have the StemWijzer a tool that calculates for which person to vote depending on your position on some statements. In Colombia they did not have such a tool yet. So I decided to make a template application which can work for any country. The only thing you need is a list of statements where you can agree with or not. And a list of persons of which you know their positions on those statements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of lists of different length to a data frame</title>
      <link>/post/list-of-lists-of-different-length-to-a-data-frame/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/list-of-lists-of-different-length-to-a-data-frame/</guid>
      <description>When scraping data from an internet page it is commun that it is not nicely formatted in table kind of way. To me it happens a lot that you get a list of lists and that the second layer of lists have different lengths. To convert this kind of data can be tricky so I made an example here. It is a shiny application that reads data from the eredivisie beach site and uses it to culculate the current standings for the wildcards for the EC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animations in Shiny using TweenLite</title>
      <link>/post/animations-in-shiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/animations-in-shiny/</guid>
      <description>From a colleague I heard about TweenLite, a JavaScript library that can be used to animate objects on your website. You can move elements around by controlling their speed and position. I wanted to see how well this would work in a Shiny application so I experimented a little bit with that.
The result is an application that can keep track of the score of the the weakest link, a TV game show from more than 10 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colombian Cooking</title>
      <link>/post/colombian-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/colombian-cooking/</guid>
      <description>Last December I had the opportunity to work with my friends from randommonkey. We made special about the Colombian kitchen. Part of this special was a Shiny application that can be used to search trough the Colombian recipes. Names, ingredient, region, complexity and the time required can be used to find your favorite one. After finding a recipe you can download the description.
So if you are interested in making some Mojarras fritas (and you know a little Spanish because the page is completely in Spanish) look here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>