<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Shiny on </title>
    <link>/categories/shiny/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Shiny on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/categories/shiny/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Uploading and Downloading files using Shiny</title>
      <link>/post/uploading-and-downloading-files-using-shiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/uploading-and-downloading-files-using-shiny/</guid>
      <description>When reading interesting books on my Kobo reader, I like to mark some parts of the text. Using those notes later can be difficult because they are stored on your Kobo in a *.annot file. To convert them to a readable *.txt file I made a shiny app. After converting you can you the result on-line and download it if you want. The code can be found here.
Uploading a File In shiny you can upload a file using the fileInput() function, that creates an upload control element that can be used to upload files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Voting Recommender</title>
      <link>/post/voting-recommender/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/voting-recommender/</guid>
      <description>In the Netherlands we have the StemWijzer a tool that calculates for which person to vote depending on your position on some statements. In Colombia they did not have such a tool yet. So I decided to make a template application which can work for any country. The only thing you need is a list of statements where you can agree with or not. And a list of persons of which you know their positions on those statements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>List of lists of different length to a data frame</title>
      <link>/post/list-of-lists-of-different-length-to-a-data-frame/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/list-of-lists-of-different-length-to-a-data-frame/</guid>
      <description>When scraping data from an internet page it is commun that it is not nicely formatted in table kind of way. To me it happens a lot that you get a list of lists and that the second layer of lists have different lengths. To convert this kind of data can be tricky so I made an example here. It is a shiny application that reads data from the eredivisie beach site and uses it to culculate the current standings for the wildcards for the EC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Animations in Shiny using TweenLite</title>
      <link>/post/animations-in-shiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/animations-in-shiny/</guid>
      <description>From a colleague I heard about TweenLite, a JavaScript library that can be used to animate objects on your website. You can move elements around by controlling their speed and position. I wanted to see how well this would work in a Shiny application so I experimented a little bit with that.
The result is an application that can keep track of the score of the the weakest link, a TV game show from more than 10 years ago.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colombian Cooking</title>
      <link>/post/colombian-cooking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/colombian-cooking/</guid>
      <description>Last December I had the opportunity to work with my friends from randommonkey. We made special about the Colombian kitchen. Part of this special was a Shiny application that can be used to search trough the Colombian recipes. Names, ingredient, region, complexity and the time required can be used to find your favorite one. After finding a recipe you can download the description.
So if you are interested in making some Mojarras fritas (and you know a little Spanish because the page is completely in Spanish) look here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>